<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <atom:link href="http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/infant.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <title></title>
        <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Infant-blog.html</link>

        <description></description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <category>Infant blog</category>
        <pubDate>Mon, 3 Aug 2015 17:03:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 3 Aug 2015 17:03:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <copyright>the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com</copyright>
    <item>
            <title>Handling an Infant Fever Effectively (and Other Medical Tips for Moms)</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Infant-Fever.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">50aee4ca83fb5ef2dff3b7c4018dbaec</guid><description>Does the thought of handling an infant fever leave you in cold sweats? That little plastic beeping stick can greatly reduce your mothering anxiety, yes. But it's only the first grade. You, my dear, need to graduate. You need a crash-course in effective fever management.</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 6 Apr 2013 12:29:42 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Splurge-Worthy Infant Christmas Dresses You Won't Find in Stores</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Infant-Christmas-Dresses.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">d41523e4283d2cc61ea1e420fb96c0a2</guid><description>Feeling a little bored with all the standard infant Christmas dresses out there? I hear you, sistah. In this year's edition of The Best and Brightest 
  of Christmas Dresses, I'll point you towards boutiques that specialize in WOW-factor.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 5 Dec 2012 14:29:04 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>is this a infected c section?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/is-this-a-infected-c-section.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">51b4a53aee5e4af5bbec922f4c2ff9c9</guid><description>hi i had a c section 11 weeks ago. i have a pin size whole that is still not healed i am leaking a yellow fluid that does smell. i wash the wound daily</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 5 Dec 2012 10:56:14 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>14 Newborn Costumes That Actually Fit Newborns</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Newborn-Costumes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">3784832bddbde1f3e54798a11aadf848</guid><description>When it comes to newborn costumes, Sturgeon's Law must be applied. What?!? You don't know this Universal Truth? Let me whittle it down to 5 words. 90% of everything is crap.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 3 Oct 2012 15:12:44 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Are Infant Halloween Costumes a Big Waste of Time?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Infant-Halloween-Costumes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">58793aa009b20bae4e23e6b213e80a4e</guid><description>Halloween is approaching and you've got a decision to make. Should you browse through endless infant Halloween costumes? Or skip the holiday altogether? Well...</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2012 15:53:31 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Infant Milestone Marker:  My Gift for You</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Milestone-Marker.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">19de199bfeb4bdb8384d19d6e43a71e4</guid><description>The Milestone Marker is my free gift for subscribing.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 6 Jun 2012 14:39:43 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Get Free Baby Coupons (Without Being Conned)</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Free-Baby-Coupons.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">b1033770f4ef8a2b94c4ebccac4c3871</guid><description>Have you fallen for the 'ole  free baby coupons con? Have you given away your precious email for a supposed-lifetime supply of baby coupons, 
only to discover you have to complete 5 so-called-offers? (Does it seem like I'm writing from experience here? 'cause I am...)</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 2 Jun 2012 19:17:59 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Why is my 8 month old baby's poo very pale?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/why-is-my-8-month-old-babys-poo-very-pale.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">e78a80e02825d7749b786cbe9e67bff4</guid><description>My baby is 8 months.  Eating solids very well and on minimal milk +- 500ml at the most per day.  She has been in hospital 3 times with bronchitus and pneumonia.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 10:49:32 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Sunblock for 4 month old</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/sunblock-for-4-month-old.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">291ae33224c226d49de4c60634264141</guid><description>Hi there, was wondering if you know of any sunblocks that are safe for 4month olds? I have heard that Episencial Sunny Sunscreen may be, but I'm not positive.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2012 10:41:22 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Baby Coupons and Discount Codes for January - February, 2012</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Baby-Coupons.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">2458a6964c01ae392039704b510a33c8</guid><description>With all the expenses a new baby brings to the table, is it any wonder that we ALL seem to be clambering for baby coupons these days?  
Here's a directory of the best online baby stores, with their current coupons, free shipping codes, and sales announcements.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 6 Jan 2012 13:06:44 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>What types of foods should I give my son? He is just starting table foods.</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/what-types-of-foods-should-i-give-my-son-he-is-just-starting-table-foods.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">9238510ef13e8c8d9846dc1db67c7854</guid><description>My 9 month old son just got the go ahead for strictly table foods from our doctor. I am wondering what to give him for breakfast and lunch? Dinner he eats</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 4 Jan 2012 17:39:38 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Constipation and Fever</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/constipation-and-fever.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">024c125ce15a44bd4dd8eaa14f9afda7</guid><description>My 20 month old son hasn't pooped in 3 and a half days and also has had a fever for that long, is something seriously wrong?    It is now Monday morning,</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 14:30:44 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Does a Belly Binder Really Help with Post-Cesearean Recovery?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Belly-Binder.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">8593b80aba17b56e6267b46f8ac7df55</guid><description>I've gotten a lot of questions over the years about whether a belly binder for post-c-section recovery is worth the cost. Since I'm not currently pregnant, I asked for a pregnant volunteer from my subscribers.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 15:42:19 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Baby Learning Toys: How to Find the Smartest Ones</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Baby-Learning-Toys.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6d4e51f40ddf9f89158f3f2f5bd9db2f</guid><description>If you're going to buy toys for your infant, why not choose baby learning toys that will stimulate his brain and encourage milestone growth? Here's what to
  look for in a toy worth giving.</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 14:34:43 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>A Baby Yoda Costume You Must Have</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Baby-Yoda-Costume.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">c1736138987f7066c530b8cddc74d95e</guid><description>If Yoda was here, he would give you some very sound advice: a baby Yoda costume you must have...Who are you to argue with the last Jedi Master? Here are some of the cutest Star Wars inspired costumes for babies in the galaxy.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2011 19:37:23 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>New Mom of Twins Needs Some Advice</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/new-mom-of-twins-needs-some-advice.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ccc960d7fd2df9046546bef3e9b444d7</guid><description>I have just given birth to twin boys on August 23rd 2011. I also have two precious girls (aged 5  and 4 years old, there is exactly a difference of one</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2011 12:01:25 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>5 Halloween Infant Costumes Inspired by Beloved Bedtime Books</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Halloween-Infant-Costumes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">25fa1438ab438ec59ad291f367ce42dc</guid><description>Don't just do Halloween infant costumes for the sake of Baby's First Halloween. Show off his emerging personality! Use his well-loved, well-chewed boardbook lying next to the nursery rocking chair 
as inspiration!</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 5 Sep 2011 09:39:40 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Transform Tom Arma Halloween Costumes into Nursery Art</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Tom-Arma-Halloween-Costumes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">a4d9016460033b66292a9f00875b0fd5</guid><description>There's a reason Tom Arma Halloween costumes are called heirlooms. They are a step WAAAY above the average Halloween infant costume. These are works of art, ready to be photographed and displayed in your nursery (or at Grandma's house) all year round.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 18:59:40 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>What are the Best Baby Monitors?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/what-are-the-best-baby-monitors.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">45b60a1b80525355eac3afaa997f2253</guid><description>I'm having my first child this Christmas and the one item i have not been able to figure out is which is the best baby monitor. I was wondering what you</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2011 09:43:42 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Help with my son... He has silent reflux!</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/help-with-my-son-he-has-silent-reflux.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ec8a5536301b6a2f0c7fd141fa8beffa</guid><description>At 3 weeks and 2 days my son began an eating frenzy, I figured he's going through a growth spurt.  2 days later, he begins fussing while he eats and burps.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 15:48:18 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>MAM Anti Colic Bottle Review</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/mam-anti-colic-bottle-review.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6c2f336e254e0d852342f52c40ff5870</guid><description>I had a hard time breast feeding my son when he was born because of my low milk supply (finally found out due to overmedicating thyroid meds) and because</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2011 19:47:53 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Free Baby Samples That Will Make Your Heart Flutter</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Free-Baby-Samples.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">8676fe5454a3b7c34179f6935d95d02f</guid><description>I recognize that the phrase free baby samples is not as breath-catching, as say...a free SUV.  However. We moms have to take our thrills where we can. Babies ain't cheap, and in my
book, every penny saved on baby stuff is a penny spent on a romantic get away with my hubby.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 9 Aug 2011 19:01:13 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Is it normal for a child with tubes in their ears to have excessive smell?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/is-it-normal-for-a-child-with-tubes-in-their-ears-to-have-excessive-smell.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">439cdbdf10008531eee0162a82a05594</guid><description>My grandson has tubes in his ears,and has had infection in them for quite some time.  He has been on antibiotic ear drops the whole time, but the smell</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 1 Aug 2011 10:21:04 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Get a Baby Food Organizer...Save a Life in Africa?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Baby-Food-Organizer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">8599fc58d1207848f05e71a73a6ffbb0</guid><description>Did you know that, for a limited time, purchasing a baby food organizer could help save a life in Africa?</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 17:00:08 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>6 Week Old Strains a Lot to Pass Gas</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/6-week-old-strains-a-lot-to-pass-gas.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">f3ffb87ba7b6566858c6bbe019d6e704</guid><description>My son is 6 weeks old and is exclusively breastfed. Since birth he used to poop after every feed. On Wednesday morning was the last time he went and started</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 10:38:46 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Reoccuring Clogged Milk Ducts &#x26; Crying....</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/reoccuring-clogged-milk-ducts-crying.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">052e2ceec5a2e6bfed0046222e250ff4</guid><description>I have had the same side clogging off &amp; on for the last 2 wks. Any tips? I've tried the whole gamit; wet compress, heating pad, hot shower, massage, even</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 09:38:44 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>My Baby is Suffering From Fever with Cough and Vomit</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/my-baby-is-suffering-from-fever-with-cough-and-vomit.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">e1ac6cc7ded397d73d0a57a22e6d398f</guid><description>My Baby is 9 Months old and she is very weak her head size is bigger in compare with her body.  In the past she suffered from fever but cured by the grace</description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 09:17:59 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Choosing the Best Baby Bottle For...</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Best-Baby-Bottle.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">743c2c368d531a89060cf874f91a0d04</guid><description>Find the best baby bottle for YOUR situation. Do you breastfeed? On a budget? Colic? Each situation has bottles that 
are best for THAT situation. Discover what they are.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 19:38:45 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>The Best Summer Reading Books</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Books-Summer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">b1dfbf1c9f3f0ca6c296ee3df5bacc40</guid><description>Merry Mothers share their favorites just in time for summer reading.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 08:59:44 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Your 2011 Infant Swimwear and Baby Fun-Sun Guide</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Infant-Swimwear.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">57665925325f625f9d31e40b0bf1c0cb</guid><description>Summer has arrived, and you're itching to breakout the infant swimwear and introduce your baby to the wonders of the outdoors. Here's everything
you need to make baby's first summer spectacular.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 21:17:10 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>5 Breastfeeding Challenges You CAN Overcome</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Breastfeeding-Challenges.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">addbb76371efc1ba79a5a0da32a44584</guid><description>There are 5 common breastfeeding challenges that often confront new mothers.  Luckily, you don't need to throw in the burp rag and give up!  You
can overcome these challenges easily.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 11:19:57 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Free Baby Diapers: Your EZ Guide to Huggies, Pampers, 7th Generation, and a Little Luvs</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Free-Baby-Diapers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">e7b68f0222ac046c747d1bb75c0c6d0c</guid><description>Okay...bad news first. (I'm such a pessimist.) Free baby diapers are not going to gently float down from heaven, covering you with their money-saving
goodness. They're more likely to arrive like Forest Gump's feather: one lonely diaper at a time.  HOWEVER, there's one thing you can do that will shake the goose, so to speak.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 6 May 2011 15:07:18 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Is Your Baby Sunscreen a Sultan? or a Sham?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Baby-Sunscreen.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4e26a06722924899b1f125b6433888b6</guid><description>I counted out eight different types of baby sunscreen at the checkout counter in Target last week. And every last one of them was taunting me. Which one should I choose? What makes each different? Does it even matter? Or is it the same white stuff in a different colored bottle?</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 2 May 2011 17:44:09 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Is my infant urinating enough?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/is-my-infant-urinating-enough.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">d986d18acf35452203a38b6a4dc058ba</guid><description>My son will be 6 months old on the 1st of May, he drinks plenty of fluids through out the day but only urinates a little in 10 hours is this normal?  </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 2 May 2011 15:58:34 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>The Baby Fever Fighter: Five Tricks To Try at Home</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Baby-Fever.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">f2fe201fe63eb62d812ad783a37a3b62</guid><description>That wicked baby fever.  His sad, tired eyes.  Your anxious ones.  Not fun.  Fortunately, you don't have to just cross your fingers and hope for the best.  I've researched up
five techniques to help you help him get more comfortable.  And when he's more comfortable, he'll eat better, sleep better, and most importantly, feel better.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2011 17:07:17 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Infant Thermometer Showdown: The Top 5 Most-Loved</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Infant-Thermometer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">fe3678e91c942a5628412a0ee1e0014d</guid><description>If I had a quarter for every infant thermometer I've purchased, I could pay cash for our health insurance. So writing this article was somewhat selfish. I wanted to get down and dirty into the world of baby thermometers. 
Pull out the medical research...poll some moms...and see which methods and tools came out shining.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2011 12:38:41 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>5 Ways to Conquer the Infant Cold</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Infant-Cold.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">818d30a759d3ac190e0075eb0248ecf0</guid><description>It is not uncommon for an infant cold to be the first storm a mother must weather. It's so hard to see your infant all stuffed up and uncomfortable! Here are some
basic guideliness on how to relieve cold-induced misery.</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2011 17:31:43 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Can Enfamil Cause Ear Infections?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/can-enfamil-cause-ear-infections.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">d56ace825a7289ecfd9d64648c886132</guid><description>This could be coincidence, but I started her on Enfamil Premium when she was 3 months old because that's what WIC offers, and that's when she started these</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 6 Apr 2011 12:10:44 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Burping Baby Tips</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Burping-Baby.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">55382a657a028aaa195f640521dafe44</guid><description>Would you be comfortable with a huge balloon in your stomach? A burping baby lives without that discomfort.  Consequence?  A happier baby.  Lesson?  Learn how to get that burp!</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 4 Apr 2011 17:17:32 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Stylish Baby Easter Dresses for Picture-Perfect Egg Hunting Adventures</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Baby-Easter-Dresses.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">e898b8aace437d03bf44b457da180530</guid><description>Let me rescue you from the hum-drum baby Easter dresses lined up at your local mega-mart.  As your friendly neighborhood fashion pirate, allow me to reveal a treasure map to the most sophisticatedly 
cute baby Spring dresses ever made. There's a New World of infant style just waiting for you to plunder.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2011 16:34:07 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Why does my baby spit up so much?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/why-does-my-baby-spit-up-so-much.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00d8bd90667e74c8660d45b31c64084b</guid><description>My son is 5 weeks old and seems to spit up everything he eats. I breastfeed and after every feeding he spits or throws up everything he just ate. He is</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 15:00:36 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Fancy Infant Easter Dresses...The 2011 Fantastics</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Infant-Easter-Dresses.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">be0184e4ca4c00ee6578a490c2ac54bc</guid><description>Forget the plain-jane infant Easter dresses stocked hundreds-high at your local Target. Go original in 2011. I've scoured the web
for amazingly-beautiful and jaw-dropping unique designs from boutiques you probably didn't even realize existed.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 14:59:10 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Are Dogs and Babies a Recipe for Grief? or a Grand Slam?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Dogs-and-Babies.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">34f8c45448f1e17e797564549accf501</guid><description>Dogs and babies are two of my passions. So when we first discovered my pregnancy, I was a little concerned. How would Moxie, the little shih tzu who had been with me since the 8th grade, handle
this new competition? Fortunately, there's a way to keep your family intact, without sending away your four-legged baby just when your two-legged one arrives.</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 17:03:27 -0400</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Why a Good Teething Pacifier Makes All The Difference</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Teething-Pacifier.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">8f8436af132ff02bd319aa9df6503c1e</guid><description>Using a regular 'ole binky as a teething pacifier is asking for trouble.  In no time all, your budding piranah will devour that flimsy plastic
and choking hazards will sprout everywhere.  You need a REAL teething pacifier, or at least some decent teething toys.  Here are the top gnaw-worthy toys to soothe and comfort your suffering infant.</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 14:40:07 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Infant Diarrhea after Formula Switch</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/infant-diarrhea-after-formula-switch.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">9e9e30ed0688b1a327b8f923e9c72c2a</guid><description>My 3 week old infant had diarrhea twice in 4 hours, what should I do?  We switched formulas from Similac Sensitive because of constipation and gave her</description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2011 15:58:17 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>A C-Section Recovery: Elizabeth's Tips for Quicker Healing</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/C-Section.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">dc3281161e325b851b001b241adee000</guid><description>Every single person on the planet (excepting any residing in Area 51), arrived either by vaginal or c-section delivery.  And although the end prize (a baby) is the same,
the methods couldn't be further apart.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 16:14:27 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Can Baby Sign Language Delay Speech?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Baby-Sign-Language.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">d3bfef89f122f8f23794d910f71b6f27</guid><description>It's a valid question.  After all, who wants to work hard teaching baby sign language only to discover it delayed the 'Mommy!' you're dying to hear?  
Yes, in the short-run baby signing is a blessing.  A signing infant will give you fewer fits of frustration.  But is that short-term benefit worth a potential long term harm?</description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 8 Jan 2011 20:57:51 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Can I give my 18 month old cold medicine?</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/can-i-give-my-18-month-old-cold-medicine.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">68c2c5876d1a490db2f3294c93bdca8f</guid><description>What cold medicine can I give my 18 month old who has greenish mucus and a constant runny nose?  Yes, he is still teething, but all this drainage is making</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 17:25:05 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>
    <item>
            <title>Skip the Baby Cold: How to Avoid the Crusty Nose Nasties</title>
            <link>http://www.the-essential-infant-resource-for-moms.com/Baby-Cold.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">001bed261cda6226c807d8cb31bed11b</guid><description>Don't let a baby cold turn your beautiful infant into a nightmare of crusty yellow nasties.  You CAN have a hugable baby all winter long.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 18:03:23 -0500</pubDate>
        </item>        
    </channel>
</rss>
